(this.webpackJsonp12_lights_out_game=this.webpackJsonp12_lights_out_game||[]).push([[0],{16:function(e,r,s){},17:function(e,r,s){},18:function(e,r,s){},20:function(e,r,s){},22:function(e,r,s){"use strict";s.r(r);var t=s(1),i=s.n(t),n=s(8),a=s.n(n),o=(s(16),s(17),[{Answer:"Xavier",Question:" _____ Institute is the home of the X-Men","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ghost",Question:"____ Rider, Marvel's motorcyle-riding superhero","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ghost Rider",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Foggy",Question:"_____ Nelson, the Daredevil's law partner","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Daredevil",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Pepper",Question:"_____ Potts is Tony Stark's romantic interest","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Infinity",Question:"_____ Stones allow whoever wields them to have god-like powers","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Silver",Question:"_____ Surfer, servant of Galactus who bretrayed him to save Earth","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Silver Surfer",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Scarlet",Question:"_____ Witch, twin sister of Quicksilver","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"39",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Drax",Question:"_____, the Destroyer","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"20",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Black",Question:"______ Cat, ","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"12",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Amazing Spider-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Jessica",Question:"______ Jones, a superhero turned private investigator","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"53",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Jessica Jones",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Winter",Question:"_______ Soldier","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"15",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Invisible",Question:"_______ Woman, one of the Fantastic Four","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"40",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Professor",Question:"_______ X is the leader of the X-Men","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"36",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Daredevil",Question:"A blind superhero who is a lawyer by day","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"40",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Daredevil",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hercules",Question:"A character based on Greek mythology and a member of the Avengers","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Talos",Question:"A cunning spy of the Skrull Empire, a master shapeshifter","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain Marvel",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hawkeye",Question:"a deaf super hero","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"17",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Nightcrawler",Question:"A devout Catholic with a demonic appearance","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"43",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Lockjaw",Question:"a giant Inhuman bulldog whose super abilities include teleportation","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"67",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Inhumans",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Inhumans",Question:"a group of\xa0Marvel superheroes\xa0whose stories focus on the royal family","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Inhumans",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Venom",Question:"a sentient alien\xa0symbiote\xa0with an amorphous form needs to bond with a host to survive ","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"86",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Amazing Spider-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"SHIELD",Question:"a special\xa0law enforcement and\xa0counter-terrorism\xa0agency in the MCU","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Punisher",Question:"A vigilante who wears a skull like logo on his body armor","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"The Punisher",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Beast",Question:"A X-Men mutant possessing animal-like strength and agility","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Warlock",Question:'Adam ________,  a synthetic being created by human scientists named "The Enclave"',"Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"81",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Silver Surfer",Question:"an alien with metallic skin who travels through space riding a surfboard","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Silver Surfer",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Vision",Question:'an\xa0android\xa0built by Ultron to be the "perfect being" who helps defeat Ultron',"Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"76",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Scott Lang",Question:"Ant-Man's secret identity","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"25",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ant-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Drax",Question:"Arthur Douglas we recreated as ______ to destroy Thanos","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"55",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Mansion",Question:"Avenger's _____ is where these superheroes live","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Rocket",Question:"bio-engineered animal who is part of the Guardians of the Galaxy","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Bolt",Question:"Black _____, king of the Inhumans, who must remain silent","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Inhumans",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hulk",Question:"Bruce Banner is _____","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"21",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Hulk",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Winter Soldier",Question:"Bucky Barnes is _______","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"23",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"America",Question:"Captain ______","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"14",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Britain",Question:"Captain ______, ","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"16",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Marvel",Question:"Captain ______, the most powerful female super hero","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"51",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain Marvel",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Steve Rogers",Question:"Captain America's secret identity","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Danvers",Question:"Carol ______, Captain Marvel's secret identity","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain Marvel",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Marvel",Question:"Carol Danvers is also known as Captain ________","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain Marvel",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hawkeye",Question:"Clint Barton is _____","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"21",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Drax",Question:"Created by Mentor & Kronos to destroy Thanos","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Strange",Question:"Doctor _____","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"12",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Strange",Question:"Doctor Strange first appeared in ______ Tales","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Sanctorum",Question:"Doctor Strange's home is called Sanctum _______","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Beast",Question:"Dr. Hank McCoy is also the ________","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"35",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Doctor Strange",Question:"Dr. Stephen _______","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"19",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Agamotto",Question:"Dr. Strange wears the Eye of _____ around his neck","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"50",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Frost",Question:"Emma _____, once a villain, later joins the X-Men","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Luke Cage",Question:"Failed prison experiment gave him unbreakable skin & superhuman strength","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Luke Cage",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Helicarrier",Question:"flying aircraft carrier, S.H.I.E.L.D.mobile command center","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Howard Stark",Question:"Founder of Stark Industries","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"27",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Castle",Question:"Frank _______, the Punisher","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"27",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"The Punisher",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Punisher",Question:"Frank Castle is the __________","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Rocket",Question:"Groot's best friend","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"19",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hogan",Question:"Happy _____ is Tony Starks driver, body guard, and assistant","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"60",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Suspense",Question:"Hawkeye made his first appearance in Tales of ______","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"52",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Heimdall",Question:"he guards the Bifrost Bridge","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Drax",Question:"His family was killed by Thanos, he now lives to get revenge","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"60",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wakanda",Question:"Home of the Black Panther","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"25",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Duckworld",Question:"Howard the Duck comes from the planet","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Howard the Duck",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Cigars",Question:"Howard the Duck smokes _______","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Howard the Duck",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Tony Stark",Question:"Iron-Man's secret identity","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"26",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"War Machine",Question:"James Rhodes is ________","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"24",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Grey",Question:"Jean ____, member of the X-Men","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ghost Rider",Question:"Johnny Blaze is _______","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"23",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ghost Rider",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Shawowcat",Question:"Kitty Pryde is also _________, and a member of the X-Men","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Captain America",Question:"Known for his shield","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"20",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Cage",Question:"Luke ____, married Jessica Jones","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"32",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Luke Cage",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Watson",Question:"Mary Jane _____, married Peter Parker/Spider-Man","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"48",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Amazing Spider-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hawkeye",Question:"Master archer, member of the Avengers","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Shang-Chi",Question:"master of the Ten Rings","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"23",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Shang-Chi",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Vibranium",Question:"metal prized for its virtually indestructable nature, only found in\xa0Wakanda","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"75",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Fantastic",Question:"Mr. _______, can stretch his body like rubber","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wasp",Question:"Nadia Pym is ______","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"19",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ant-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Romanova",Question:"Natasha __________, also known as the Black Widow","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Black Widow",Question:"Natasha Romanoff is _____","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"25",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Dormannu",Question:"Nemesis of Dr. Strange from the Dark Dimension","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"Fury",Question:"Nick _____, Director of SHIELD","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Groot",Question:'Only says "I am _____"',"Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"22",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Carter",Question:"Peggy _____, love interest of Captain America","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Star-Lord",Question:"Peter Quill is _______","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"22",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Coulson",Question:"Phil _____, SHIELD agent","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"24",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wong",Question:"Protects the New York Sanctum with Doctor Strange","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Richards",Question:"Reed ________, leader of the Fantastic Four","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"43",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Jones",Question:"Rick _____, Hulk's closest confidant","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"36",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Hulk",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Raccoon",Question:"Rocket is a bio-engineered ______","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Halfworld",Question:"Rocket Raccoon comes from Planet ______","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"39",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Falcon",Question:"Sam Wilson is the ________","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"26",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ant Man",Question:"Scott Lang","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"10",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ant-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Groot",Question:"Sentient alien tree that keeps the universe safe","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"48",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Yondo",Question:'Star Lord\'s "adopted" father',"Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ego",Question:"Star Lord's father","Answer Letters":"3","Question Letters":"18",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Captain America",Question:"Steve Rogers is ______","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"22",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Thing",Question:"Stony giant who is one of the Fantastic Four","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Black Panther",Question:"T'Challa is ________","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"20",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ancient",Question:"The ______ One, is Soccer Supreme & Dr. Strange's mentor","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Avengers",Question:"The _______ is a team of Marvel superheroes","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"43",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"X-Men",Question:"The Beast first appeared in ","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Levitation",Question:"The Cloak of ______ is worn by Dr. Strange","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"42",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Valkyrie",Question:"The goddess Brunnhilde, one of Asgard's mightiest warriors","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Asgard",Question:"The home of Thor, Odin and the Valkyrie","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"39",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Jarvis",Question:"The loyal butler to the Stark family","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"36",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Sam Wilson",Question:"The secret identity of the 2nd Captain America","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Danger",Question:"The X-Men train in the specially built_______ Room","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"50",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Loki",Question:"Thor's adopted brother","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"22",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Iron Man",Question:"Tony Stark is ______","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"20",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Klaue",Question:"Ulysses _____, in Black Panther","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"31",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Angel",Question:"Warren Kenneth Worthington III is an X-man, also known as","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Thanos",Question:"Wiped out half the population of the universe","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Star-Lord",Question:'Yondo\'s "adopted" son',"Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"21",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Spiderman",Question:"Your friendly neighborhood _______","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"34",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"The Amazing Spider-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Absorbing",Question:"______ Man, can take on the properties of any material he touches","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Barracuda",Question:"A ruthless criminal and assissin who hunted the Punisher","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Cannonball",Question:"Human ______, is supervillian appearing in Marvel comics","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Chameleon",Question:"Spider-man's first adversay in The Amazing Spider-Man #1","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Deathstrike",Question:"Laky _______, ","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Dormammu",Question:"one of Doctor Strange's fiercest advesaries","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Galactus",Question:"a\xa0cosmic entity\xa0that consumes planets to sustain its life force","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Green Goblin",Question:"Norman Osborn turns into the","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Green Goblin",Question:"a\xa0Halloween-themed supervillain that flies on a hoverboard","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Juggernaut",Question:"a villian whose head is like a battering ram","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Kingpin",Question:"a\xa0crime overlord, advesary of Spider-Man,Daredevil,\xa0Hawkeye, andthe\xa0Punisher","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Kraven",Question:"_______, the Hunter, one of Spider-Man's advesaries","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Maximus",Question:"both a member of and antagonist to the\xa0Inhumans","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Morbius",Question:"A vampire inspired Spider-Man advesary, he became an antihero\xa0with his own series","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"81",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Mastermind",Question:"Jason Wyngrade, is also the supervillian _______","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Molten Man",Question:"One of Spider-Man's early advesaries, his body can generate extreme heat and radiation","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Norman",Question:"____ Osborn, global industrialist and the Green Goblin","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Octopus",Question:"Doctor _____, Spider-man's first villian","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Omega",Question:"_______ Red, ","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Puppet",Question:"______ Master, first appeared in Fantastic Four #8","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Rhino",Question:"A green colored villian with a horn on his head, early Spider-Man advesary","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Ronan",Question:"______ the Accuser, is the Supreme Accuser of the\xa0Kree Empire and works with Thanos","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Sinister",Question:"Mr. ______, ","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Sentinels",Question:"mutant-hunting\xa0robots, usually advesaries of the\xa0X-Men.","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Collector",Question:"created a massive museum of life forms and artifacts from across the MCU","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Ultron",Question:"a self-aware, highly intelligent robot who develops a\xa0god complex\xa0and a grudge against his creator\xa0Hank Pym","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Vulture",Question:"Adrian Toomes is the flying supervillian called the _______","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Struker",Question:"Baron von _______ is an eneny of SHIELD and the Avengers","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Sinister",Question:"the _______ Six, a group of villians organized by Doctor Octopus","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Sinister Six",Question:"a group originallly composed of Doc Oc, Vulture, Electro, Mysterio, Sandman & Kraven","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Enforcers",Question:"Team of villians originally consisting of Montana, the\xa0Ox, and\xa0Fancy Dan","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Cerebro",Question:"Device created by Professor X to detect humans and mutants","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Skrulls",Question:"a race of extraterrestial shapeshifters who appear in many Marvel comic series","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Destroyer",Question:"an animated suit of Asguardian armor that plagues Thor","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Hydra",Question:"Baron von Strucker's terrorist organization prominent in the MCU","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""},{Answer:"Thanos",Question:"a powerful villian in the\xa0MCU, he has a twisted moral compass and thinks his actions are justified.","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:""}]),u=s(2),l=(s(18),s(0));function y(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:"-",r=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]&&arguments[1],s=arguments.length>2&&void 0!==arguments[2]&&arguments[2],i=Object(t.useState)(r),n=Object(u.a)(i,2),a=n[0],o=n[1],l=Object(t.useState)(s),y=Object(u.a)(l,2),_=y[0],h=y[1],f=Object(t.useState)(""),c=Object(u.a)(f,2),w=c[0],v=c[1],A=Object(t.useState)(e),S=Object(u.a)(A,2),L=S[0],C=S[1],g=[],Q={state:a,setState:o,special:_,setSpecial:h,letter:L,setLetter:C,position:g,attemptLetter:w,setAttempt:v};return Q}function _(e){var r="",s="";return e.context.state?(r="Cell",r+=e.context.special?" Cell-Glow":" Cell-Input",s=e.context.special?e.context.letter:Object(l.jsx)("input",{type:"text",onFocus:function(){var r;r=e.context,(0,e.setRow)(r.position[0]),console.log("row",r.position[0])},onChange:function(r){!function(e,r){r.setSpecial(e.target.value.toLowerCase()==r.letter.toLowerCase())}(r,e.context,e.setRow)}})):r="Space",Object(l.jsx)("td",{className:r,children:Object(l.jsx)("p",{className:"CellContent",children:s})})}s(20);var h=s(6);function f(e){return Object(l.jsx)(v,{dimensions:S(e),word:e.word,data:e.data})}var c=[];function w(e){c=[];for(var r=parseInt(e.dimensions.width/2),s=0;s<e.dimensions.height;s++){for(var t=[],i=e.data[s].Answer,n=i.indexOf(e.data[s].Letter),a=0,o=0;o<e.dimensions.width;o++){var u={},h=r-n;o>=h&&o<r+i.length-n?(u=y(i[a],!0,o-h==e.data[s].Index),a++):u=y(""),u.position=[s,o],t.push(u)}c.push(t)}var f=Object(l.jsx)("tbody",{children:c.map((function(r,s){return t=r,i=s,Object(l.jsx)("tr",{children:t.map((function(r,s){return Object(l.jsx)(_,{setRow:e.context.setRow,context:r},"".concat(i,",").concat(s))}))},i);var t,i}))});return f}function v(e){var r=Object(h.useState)(!1),s=Object(u.a)(r,2),t=s[0],i=s[1],n=Object(h.useState)(0),a=Object(u.a)(n,2),o={hasWon:t,setHasWon:i,row:a[0],setRow:a[1]};return Object(l.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(l.jsxs)("div",{className:"Board-title",children:[Object(l.jsx)("div",{className:"neon-orange",children:"Hero"}),Object(l.jsx)("div",{className:"neon-blue",children:"Trivia"})]}),Object(l.jsx)("table",{className:"Board",children:Object(l.jsx)(w,{dimensions:e.dimensions,word:e.word,data:e.data,context:o})}),Object(l.jsx)(A,{data:e.data,context:o})]})}function A(e){var r=e.data[e.context.row].Question;return Object(l.jsx)("div",{className:"Question-container",children:Object(l.jsx)("div",{className:"Question-content",children:r})})}function S(e){var r,s=0;return r=e.word.length,e.data.forEach((function(e){s<e.Answer.length&&(s=e.Answer.length)})),{width:2*s,height:r}}s(7);var L=s(11);s(9),s(10);function C(e){var r=[];return o.forEach((function(s){s.Answer.indexOf(e)>-1&&r.push(s)})),r}function g(e,r){var s=[];return r.forEach((function(r){if(s.length!=e)s.push(r);else for(var t=0;t<s.length;t++)s[t].Answer.length>r.Answer.length&&(s[t]=r)})),s}var Q="Skyler";function M(e){var r=parseInt(Math.random()*o.length),s=function(e){var r=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]&&arguments[1],s=[];return Object(L.a)(e).forEach((function(e){var t=C(e),i=(t[t.length-1],g(3,t)),n=parseInt(100*Math.random()%i.length),a={};a=r?{Letter:e,Index:t[n].Answer.indexOf(e),Question:t[n].Question,Answer:t[n].Answer,"Answer Letters":t[n]["Answer Letters"],"Question Letters":t[n]["Question Letters"],Category:t[n].Category,Publisher:t[n].Publisher,Series:t[n].Series,Universe:t[n].Universe,Difficulty:t[n].Difficulty}:{Letter:e,Index:t[n].Answer.indexOf(e),Question:t[n].Question,Answer:t[n].Answer},s.push(a)})),s}(Q=o[r].Answer);return Object(l.jsx)("div",{className:"App",children:Object(l.jsx)(f,{word:Q,data:s})})}var d=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&s.e(3).then(s.bind(null,23)).then((function(r){var s=r.getCLS,t=r.getFID,i=r.getFCP,n=r.getLCP,a=r.getTTFB;s(e),t(e),i(e),n(e),a(e)}))};a.a.render(Object(l.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(l.jsx)(M,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),d()}},[[22,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.5e01cb85.chunk.js.map